# VIVEK AGRAVAT

#### **PROFILE**

I enjoy to be as an Programmer and Developer where extensive experience will be further developed and utilized. Extensive experience to the credit. I always wonder to be a part of IT, Development that can make the world more better place



### REACH ME



+64 221858823



vivek.agravat177@gmail.com

## EDUCATION

2017 - RUNNING OTAGO POLYTECHNIC

Graduate diploma in I.T.

2014 - 2016 CPI OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

**Masters of Computer Applications** 

2010 - 2014 S.S.C.C.S

Bachelor of Computer Applications

#### SKILLS

iOS App development

PHP

Database management

MS Office

EXPERTISE

**SWIFT LANGUAGE** 

**MVC ARCHITECTURE** 

**PROJECT MANAGEMENT** 

**TEAM LEADING IN PROJECTS** 

# **EXPERIENCE**

# January 2016 HYPERLINK INFOSYSTEM

Internship

- Worked as iOS developer with live project from scratch
- Mainly faced applications like Taxi and multimedia.
- Geo location, tracking, in-app purchase, audio and video management, REST api support all of glimpse of my work.

## July 2016 - June 2017 HYPERLINK INFOSYSTEM

Junior iOS developer

- Perform overviews of development operations of a application in order to maintenance and it run efficiently.
- Analyse application requirement and customer trend.
- Prepares asset, liability, and resources entries by compiling and analyzing client information.

# January 2015 - January 2016 SAMAY LTD.

### **Customer Support**

- Worked as customer support in Samay ltd. is fun and most learning phase in my college days.
- Inbound and out bound calling is part of my work
- Report management and profile update is daily routine in the job.

## FREELANCE WORK

http://www.tolan.ca/
https://www.kellyfidel.com/

http://www.ashishdesaiadvocate.com/index.html

http://www.coveritup.in/

https://www.themerchantice.com/